# CHRISTIAN RAY

1502 E Sumner Ave, Indianapolis, IN 46227 | christianray1502@gmail.com (704) 649-7041

#### **SUMMARY**

Enthusiastic Customer Service Provider with over three years of experience in the service industry. Committed to providing a strong customer service experience across settings, and to personal growth and development. Strategic in blending organizational skills and education to work well and communicate effectively with patrons, colleagues and supervisors. Proven ability to lead in the workplace.

#### **SKILLS**

- Good written and oral communication skills
- Effectively communicate and collaborate with internal and external stakeholders
- Strong organizational skills, being able to function in a fast-paced environment
- Ability to interact with all levels of management and work in a team environment
- Understands and implements processes and procedures

- Strong work ethic
- Adaptable
- Team player
- Flexible
- Organized
- Reflective
- Leadership skills
- Collaborative
- Communicative

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# 7/2019 to 7/2022 Customer Service Representative/ Leadership Team/ Training Team/ Manager in Training

Chick Fil-A – Belmont, NC

- Provided strong customer service delivery to patrons across settings and platforms
- Continued in learning activities/training opportunities to build and grow skill sets; participated in cross team training
- Successfully utilized technology platforms relevant to job performance
- Collaborated with team members to identify and accomplish organization objectives.
- Assisted in team development by training new employees while maintaining customer service delivery
- Established and maintained working relationships within and across teams in a fast pace working environment
- Recruited to Leadership Team and responsible for working with Team to build and implement new programs within the context of customer service delivery model

#### 11/2020 to 1/2021 Warehouse Associate

Amazon.com Inc. - Charlotte, NC

- Provided accurate and attentive detail to sorting of packages in a timely manner
- Worked and assisted when not required to ensure the productivity and efficiency of necessary job functions.

- Successfully utilized technology platforms relevant to job performance
- Able to maintain efficient and timely performance in a fast pace working environment.
- Worked in a cooperative and efficient manner
- Created friendly and cooperative friendships with co-workers

# 7/2021 to 4/2022 Website Manager Apostolic Information Services (AIS)/ IBC Perspectives Magazine — Indianapolis, IN

- Maintained Vital Website Functions on a timely schedule, including editing and updating magazine articles and editions on to relevant website.
- Successfully communicated with Leadership to effectively create and promote Email Advertisement Campaign
- Successfully utilized technology platforms relevant to job performance
- Ability to self-manage and maintain performance independently
- Coordinated design and creation of website platform rebranding and updating according to relevant needs of leadership

## **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

#### 5/2020 Completion of Career & College Promise Associate of Science Pathway

Gaston County College — Dallas, NC

5/2020 High School Graduate (Career & College Readiness Focus)

West Belmont Academy - Belmont, NC

5/2021 Leadership Promotion and Management Training

Chick-fil-A - Belmont, NC

7/2020 Christian Leadership Major Degree Program (In Progress)

Indiana Bible College – Indianapolis, IN

1/2021 Counseling Minor Degree Program (In Progress)

Indiana Bible College – Indianapolis, IN

7/2022 Computer Science Major Program (In Progress)

Gaston Community College – Dallas, NC

#### **ACTIVITIES AND HONORS**

Taekwondo/Red Belt Plays multiple instruments; Guitar (Acoustic/ Electric), Piano Volunteer Tutor Honor Roll- multiple years

#### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Volunteer Usher, HYPHEN Youth Group Minister Zion Temple of Pentecost-Charlotte, NC Leadership Team, Chick Fil-A Training Team, Chick-Fil-A Security Director, Indiana Bible College

## Urban Missions Ministry Leader, Indiana Bible College

## **REFERENCES**

**Rev. Damon Peavy Jr.**, Youth Pastor Zion Temple of Pentecost Mount Holly, NC (980) 253-3128

**Zack Ross**, Assistant Editor and Office Manager, Previous Manager Apostolic Information Services, IBC Perspectives Magazine Indianapolis, IN (317) 801-0146

Jason Gallion, Executive Vice-President Indiana Bible College Indianapolis, IN (907) 947-0296

**Amber Hampton**, Operational Manager Chick-Fil-A Belmont, NC (704) 914-6851